Include "Further Reading" section at end with source links." 
7. The Empathy Rewriter

Prompt:

"Technical content: [paste]

Rewrite this for someone who:
- Doesn't know the jargon
- Needs to understand why they should care
- Wants to know "what do I do with this?"

For every technical term:

1. Define it in one sentence
2. Give a concrete example or analogy
3. Explain why it matters

Structure as:

- What is this? (plain English, no assumptions)
- Why should I care? (benefits, not features)
- How does it work? (simplified, with examples)
- What should I do next? (clear action step)

Test: A smart 16-year-old should understand this." 
Manufacturer, Supplier
Quality Fiber Optic Cable Manufacturer. Factory Outlets, Quotes Now.
?
Sopto Technology
?
?
?
?
?
{"mode":"full","isActive":true,"isUserDisabled":false}
{"mode":"full","isActive":true,"isUserDisabled":false}
8. Story Structure Overlay

Prompt:

"Content to improve: [paste article/report]

This is informative but boring. Rewrite using story structure:

ACT 1 - SETUP (20%)
- Start with relatable moment or specific scenario
- Introduce protagonist (can be reader, case study, or "people who...")
- Establish stakes (what happens if problem isn't solved?)

ACT 2 - CONFLICT (60%)
- Show obstacles and failed attempts
- Build tension with "but then..." moments
- Include turning point or key insight

ACT 3 - RESOLUTION (20%)
- Reveal solution or transformation
- Show before/after contrast
- End with actionable takeaway

Keep all factual content. Add narrative connective tissue.

Current tone: [tone]
Maintain: [any technical requirements]" 
9. The Polish Pass (Final Edit)

Prompt:

"Edit this for publication:

[paste draft]

Checklist:
□ Fix grammar, spelling, punctuation
□ Improve weak verbs (is/was/have → action verbs)
□ Vary sentence length (mix short punchy sentences with longer ones)
□ Remove redundancies and filler phrases
□ Strengthen opening sentence and closing paragraph
□ Add transition words where flow is choppy
□ Check that every paragraph has one clear point
